Rob Grabowski

UX/UI Designer & Developer

rob.j.grabowski@gmail.com (781) 296 - 7362 robgrabowski.com Experienced Designer & Developer advocating for the user. I believe the user is always at the core of design. I make websites and mobile apps usable so companies get more value from their customers.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Designer

January 2017 - Current

Consultant

I work with a variety of clients designing and developing their websites.

Your Private Eyestylist

- Worked with client to refine business objectives through meetings and a business/brand questionnaire.
- To understand potential customers I conducted a User Survey.
 From the User Survey results, I created User Personas and
- User Flow Diagrams.Created a Sitemap and did a content analysis based on the
- business offerings.
- Designed High-Fidelity Wireframe options.
- Presented mockups with Typeface and Color Palette options.
- Developed Responsive Home Page with javascript transitions.

Timothy Malone Wines

- Site redesign for an Oregon-based winemaker.
- Designed multiple modern wireframe options.
- Utilized the current color palette for design mockups.
- Currently developing the site.

FanDistro

April 2011 - June 2016

Director of Business Development

FanDistro provides an incentive based social media marketing platform for artists and brands. Artists incentivize and reward fans and influencers to amplify the reach and value of their social media campaigns. Brands partner with artists for their campaigns to build brand awareness. FanDistro was named by Midemlab as a 2013 Finalist in the Marketing and Social Engagement category.

- Helped build a business concept from the ground up to an award nominated company.
- Co-managed all aspects of the development cycle including UX/UI Design, Quality Assurance, Front End Development, and Database Design.
- Helped increase user signups by over 200% from doing a signup flow analysis and redesign.
- Managed brand ambassador social media marketing campaigns delivering media value to brands.
- Brokered partnerships between artists and brands.
- Assisted design of Sales outreach materials.
- Artist and user relations.

Inflexxion Software Developer

February 2008 - March 2011

Software Develope

- Built content driven websites in C# using an Ektron Content
 Management System and SQL Server.
 Set up websites to update newsletter lists using Constant
- Contact's API.

 Developed custom reports using SQL Reporting Services.
- Developed daily tracker questionnaire with printable reports
- using Telerik AJAX controls.

http://robgrabowski.com

Please take a look at my work and connect with me at

EDUCATION

West Virginia University B.S., Business Administration, Finance

1990 - 1994

2016 - 2017

Bloc

UX/UI Design

SKILLS

UX/UI Design, Sketch, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe
Photoshop, InvisionApp, Balsamiq, Logo Design, Low/
High Fidelity Wireframing, User Surveys, User Personas,
User Flow Diagrams, Sitemaps, Mockups, Typeface,
Color, Visual Hierarchy, HTML5, CSS, Javascript, JQuery,
PHP, C#, ASP.Net, MySQL, SQL Server